{
    "subject": "resource/David_Robbins_(artist)",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1957",
    "human_readable": "David Robbins (artist) was born in 1957.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8641148805618286,
            "question": "When was David Robbins born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7446333765983582,
            "question": "Is David Robbins a musician, writer, or artist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6689529418945312,
            "question": "In what year did David Robbins begin his career as an artist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5118203163146973,
            "question": "What profession is David Robbins known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43289798498153687,
            "question": "What are some notable works by David Robbins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29485267400741577,
            "question": "What is David Robbins's primary medium of artistic expression?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2850642502307892,
            "question": "Where did David Robbins receive his art training?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2818312346935272,
            "question": "What are some of the themes explored in David Robbins's art?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26108041405677795,
            "question": "Has David Robbins won any awards for his artwork?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20749132335186005,
            "question": "How has David Robbins's work influenced contemporary art?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=David Robbins (artist) was born in 1957.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1197_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has David Robbins won any awards for his artwork?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1197_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the themes explored in David Robbins's art?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1197_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did David Robbins receive his art training?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1197_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1197_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1197_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1197_155.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1197_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1197_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1197_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1197_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1197_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1197_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1197_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple, as there are multiple references to David Robbins being born in 1957 or 1958, with one source specifying Whitefish Bay, Wisconsin."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references to David Robbins being born in 1957, which supports the statement that \"David Robbins (artist) was born in 1957.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}